[Connor] Previously on Sterling Point…
[Ellis] You're her dad.
I'm sorry. I never wanted it
to come out like this.
What was your plan. then?
Did you even have one?
God. I hate being back here.
How are you not scared of it?
Because I love you.
-Oh. my God! [screams]
-Whoa!
I went to Barrie
to talk to Gordon's lawyer.
I need you to sign this.
What is it?
I don't want you to be my guardian.
[Rory] Once we get back to the city.
you'll feel like yourself again.
I may stay here. actually.
And do what?
And live.
Tell my kids they're not Canadian
and convince them to come back home.
that'd be nice.
I'd rather die than leave Sterling Point
and you and…
You were about to say Ellis.
-No.
-Yeah. you were.
-[Annie] We did kiss.
-[Ramona gasps]
[Annie] I know.
-[Ramona] Shut up.
-In the closet.
Why do you check your dad's socks for him?
'Cause he's colorblind. so he mixes up
navy blue and black.
[Sully] I think that you are
really good at hiding.
But what if you just
went ahead and faced it?
I need you to spit in a tube.
Can I ask why?
Because I think you might be my dad.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
[Annie] I cannot believe
I have to leave this place.
It's just. like. this is exactly
where I'm supposed to be.
-You know what I mean?
-Yeah.
-With exactly who I'm supposed to be with.
-Aw.
[chuckles] I'm sorry.
I should've said it more seriously.
We could write letters.
Have you ever written a letter?
-I've always wanted like a. like a…
-[Ellis] Yeah?
…Henry VIII-Anne Boleyn situation.
except. like. not. She was beheaded.
So not. like. entirely ideal.
So…
what do you want to do
with your last couple days?
["I Know A Place" playing]
Hmm…
Well. obviously this.
[all chattering indistinctly]
-[Oona] You okay?
-[Ramona] Mmm-hmm.
[Ramona] Yeah. I'm just stressed.
You can tell me if something's up.
I know.
Okay.
[speaking indistinctly]
-Cheers.
[all laughing]
-Hey.
Good morning.
-What?
-Did you get up to brush your teeth?
-No.
-[chuckles]
The truth will set you free.
You put on your makeup. It's okay.
-Can't forget the morning makeup.
-No one just looks like that.
[softly] Is this okay?
[whispers] Yeah.
[breath trembling]
[muttering] No.
I'm not interested. thank you.
No.
Okay.
Oh.
[suspenseful music playing]
Fuck.
-At least your dick works.
-[Ramona sighs]
I-- Okay.
So she is 100%
your and Mom's biological child?
[Steven] I mean. to be clear.
I didn't even think it was a possibility.
Also. Annie. this doesn't…
This doesn't change
anything between us or--
Why wouldn't you tell me the second
that you thought that this could be true?
I didn't want to freak you out
if it wasn't.
I didn't want to ruin
your last few days here for no reason.
Also. I didn't…
I didn't want it to be true.
It's not like I had this plan.
Should I get a paternity test?
Maybe I'm. like. someone's secret dad.
Okay. please.
Are you mad at me?
No. I'm not mad at you. Ramona.
I'm just…
I'm not mad at you.
I'm just processing this.
I'm just. like. wrapping my head around…
that they are your actual parents.
But didn't you say your parents
are the people who raised you?
[Steven] I think
we're all just gonna have to be
as understanding as possible
with each other about this.
Can we talk outside?
Yeah. okay.
I think I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Yeah. go for it.
Hey. um…
No. it's… Yeah. it's fine.
I actually have sympathy for you in this.
It's a wild bomb drop.
Yeah. that's one way to put it.
I just don't want to make assumptions
about what you might want from me.
I can just say. if you ever want to
come to New York…
-That's sweet. I don't. but thank you.
-[sighs]
Um. I do want you to sign off
on not being my guardian. though.
Who's gonna take care of you?
Me.
No. no. It's not sad. It's…
It's not like that.
You don't have to do that.
I'm serious. It's really not.
It's what I'm used to.
It's been that way for a while.
and I'd like to keep it that way.
That way we can all move on and…
I mean. you're thinking
we're just gonna move on?
Yeah.
-Okay. I'm gonna…
-Yeah.
[Steven] Hey.
Um…
I love you.
You're my daughter.
Nothing's gonna change that. okay?
Are you gonna turn around? Can we talk or…
Sure. But stop saying
that nothing's changed.
Literally everything's changed.
Doesn't even feel
like she's my sister anymore.
It feels like she's your daughter.
and I'm the adopted one.
Like I'm the fake sister
and the fake daughter.
and she's the one
you always actually wanted.
She's the literal miracle kid.
[Steven] Annie. come on.
None of that is true.
I'm surprised you're reacting like this.
I'm sorry that I'm having
a bit of a complicated reaction
to a really fucked-up.
complicated situation.
so I'm just gonna need you
to understand that I…
cannot be okay right now. fully.
I can't just snap my fingers and be fine.
I'm not either.
I missed Ramona's whole life.
Oh. my God! This is exactly what I mean!
-What?
-Like. it makes me so sad when you're sad.
Like. I literally can't take it.
It wrecks me. So I… Then I fix it.
But. like. I can't fix it
for you right now.
I can't fix this for you.
Obviously. I want to make this better.
and act like I'm okay. but I'm not.
'cause I'm the kid.
You know?
[exhales] I'm the kid.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't…
I know I'm not great at it. I…
But I really was…
I've been just trying to protect you
and give you the best life. but I know.
[Annie] I know. I know.
but I just feel like…
like maybe. like.
my life here is better for me.
Your life here? Really?
Like. you don't have a life here.
It's a lot realer of a life
than the bullshit one
-I have in New York. It is.
-This is a summer thing.
You've asked me one question.
What the fuck do you know about my summer?
My summer.
I don't think you're gonna get
what you're looking for.
I just don't think following
in your mom's footsteps
and trying to live the life
that she thought that she wanted
is gonna give you what you want.
It's not gonna bring her back.
It's not gonna make…
It's not gonna fix anything.
When are you gonna forgive her for dying?
Is that why you can't look at Ramona?
Because she looks so much like her?
[dramatic soft music playing]
You know. Connor.
I'm like a mother figure.
It's me. Denise.
You can talk to me about what's going on.
Aw.
Thanks. Big D.
And… if I'm gonna be for real for real.
I did take some of your mushrooms
that you keep in your bedside table.
-[scoffs]
-Frankly. I'm fucking flying.
Did you leave me any?
No. [laughs]
[laughing] It's a little bit funny.
Like. my dad and my dead mom
have a fucking real kid?
I mean. what a psychotic joke.
That raccoon looks really friendly.
Connor. honey. I don't think
you really think that this is funny.
You know. you're likely the most…
emotionally intelligent person
in your family.
And that can be a heavy weight
to carry. you know?
Thank you.
But I see you. buddy.
Do you think that raccoon has distemper?
That's a mailbox.
Okay. good. I'm glad he's okay.
[footsteps approaching]
[Ellis] Annie?
-Hey.
I was looking for you.
[slow instrumental music playing]
Are you okay?
[Oona] I think it's just gonna
take Annie a second.
Yeah. I don't know. it just feels like…
It feels so different now.
[Oona] Mmm-hmm.
Like. I feel like if I were to.
I don't know.
ever want to get to know him or. like.
visit New York.
I probably can't do that now
because I really feel like
she'd be weird about it.
Like I'm stealing her dad.
What? So. like…
are you thinking of going there
and having a relationship with him?
I don't know.
Oh.
What?
No. Nothing.
[chuckles] No. it's obviously something.
-What--
-No. no. no. I just…
I didn't know that
you'd even consider. like.
-maybe living in New York.
-I didn't say I'm moving.
If you want a relationship with him.
you'd want to live there for a bit.
Right?
Okay. I'm sorry.
What's going on right now?
No. nothing's going on.
-You seem like--
-Babe. I'm just trying to catch up.
-Sorry.
-Okay. Yeah.
Five minutes ago. you were so sure
you wanted nothing to do with that man.
Like. you were so anti that.
Like. you were talking about me
moving in with you for the winter.
-Do you still want me to do that?
-Yeah. I just…
Dude. I just found out
that my biological dad is Steven.
-Mmm-hmm.
-Steven. Like…
-I'm just talking out loud. I don't--
-Yeah. No. I know.
-Okay.
-Yeah. I'm talking out loud too.
I know how this is gonna go.
-You know how this is gonna go?
-Yes.
-Okay. tell me.
-You're gonna go to New York.
You'll like it better than here
because it's New York.
and it's exciting and cool.
and you're gonna have money.
Travel. do whatever you want.
experience all of these crazy. cool things
and you will forget about me.
You won't come back. And it is chill.
Like. Mona. so fine. I get it.
Like. can't blame you for it.
Hundred percent. Very chill.
Thought you knew me
a little better than that.
Oona. look at me. I would never do that.
-Yeah. okay.
-Like. in no world would I do that.
You say that now.
Glad to know you think so low of me. Cool.
-No. come on. It's not that.
-That's awesome. Yeah. Yeah. I'm gonna go.
No. don't leave. Ramona. We agreed
that that's the worst thing to do.
-I don't care.
-Let's just talk about it.
-You don't care?
-I don't care.
It's so clear to me right now that
you don't care what I'm going through.
The lack of empathy is crazy.
You only care about how. like.
this is gonna affect you
and your life and your happiness
and your well-being. and…
none of this is actually about me.
This is about you.
It's about you
and your fucking mommy issues.
Because you think
I'm gonna leave you like she did.
I've never given you anything
to think that. ever.
-[scoffs] Love that.
-I've literally never even left.
Well done. Well done. You just
pushed me away as far as you could.
Did you like that? Did that feel good?
-Did I like that?
-That was great.
Hit the spot. Hit the spot. baby.
Thank you. Cool.
Oona. I'm… I didn't…
Nah. it's all good. It's okay.
-We should just stop here.
-I'm sorry.
We should stop
before we hurt each other more. It's fine.
What the fuck does that mean?
You're not hurting me. I don't know…
I don't know. I just. like.
now isn't our time. and that's okay.
-Now isn't our time?
-No. It's not.
It's just not working. obviously.
-So we're just gonna break up?
-Yeah. I think we should.
I think it's what's best for us.
You think that's what's best…
So you're just. like. dictating the status
of our relationship now?
-You should go see the world.
-I don't want to go see the world.
You do. Do it.
Let me know how it is.
Have a good time.
[clears throat]
[Annie] I feel so bad about
how I handled this with Ramona.
[Ellis] It's all… It's all gonna work out.
Will it?
Yeah.
We've kind of fucking been through it
this summer. yeah?
-[both chuckle]
-I don't know what you're talking about.
That was a really uneventful summer
on my end.
Yeah. No. totally. Yeah.
God. If only something happened.
Okay. so what was more boring.
when you found out that your dad
might also be your best friend's dad.
or when we found out
that our parents had an affair?
-Yeah. that was kind of boring.
-'Cause that was pretty sick.
-Yeah.
-Um…
Neither. actually.
I think the most boring part was
watching my parents' marriage…
-Totes.
-…fall apart.
-[chuckles] Which is kind of fucked up.
-[laughs] That's brutal.
-It's funny. though. No. it's funny.
-It's not. That's why I'm not laughing.
No. please laugh.
It's the only thing we can do.
-It's fine.
-True. True.
True.
[sighs]
This face.
-I just wanna stare at it forever. What?
-Ellis. no. no.
What?
No. we don't have to…
We don't have to
make it harder for ourselves. Um…
We're gonna write
and talk and visit. It's good.
[softly] Annie.
[softly] What?
Ellis. no.
I'm gonna miss you so much.
Don't make this hurt
more than it has to. please.
[sobs] Please.
I think we…
I think we have to let this hurt.
Okay?
Yes.
No.
I don't want to leave.
[Sully] All right. I know that you said
you wanted to try
some different kinds of mushrooms.
so I got you some king mushrooms.
some enoki.
and some lobster as well.
Which one of these
will make me see raccoons again?
-What? Raccoons?
-[door opens]
-It's over.
-[Sully] What?
What… What is?
Oona broke up with me.
-No! Oh. my God. baby.
-Wait. no!
What happened? You guys were iconic.
like Bert and Ernie.
Okay. come sit. I'll be right back. okay?
Sully. don't bring me any food.
I'm gonna give you as much food as I want.
because it always makes you feel better.
-I'm gonna throw up.
-I'll be right back.
What am I supposed to do?
Annie's mad at me. and Oona hates me.
Like. I never thought I'd say this. but…
I fucking hate it here.
Like. everything just hurts.
You know what you could do?
What?
Sell that bitch.
I mean. if you sold. you could leave
and do whatever you wanted forever.
I mean. Denise already made a deal.
She handed it to me in a fancy
little folder. so we know it's legit.
And just tell Annie what you want to do.
She promised to go
with whatever your decision was.
Taking myself out of this whole deal.
I fuck with you.
And. like. this was before I knew
my dad was your sperm donor.
so. like. now it's double that.
-I fuck with you too. I guess.
-No surprise.
-Lesbians usually fuck with me.
-Okay.
[chuckles] I mean.
don't you wanna travel?
I don't know.
go to school somewhere cool. like Italy.
You're smart. Like. you read books
in not-a-performative-male kinda way.
And you look kind of Italian.
You'd probably do great there.
And. I mean.
what do you have to lose?
You've kind of already lost everything.
Right. Okay. Damn.
I'm sorry. That was… That was too far.
Okay. so. just.
hypothetically. if I were to do it…
Nothing could happen to Ellis
or the marina.
Hypothetically. you can cut
whatever you want out of the deal.
[footsteps approaching]
Hey.
I just want to
talk to you about something.
If you wanna sit down.
Okay.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
I wanna sell.
-Sell…
-Sell the island.
What?
Sorry. I. um…
I'm confused. Wha… Since when?
I realized I have nothing left here.
you know?
-What?
-Gordon's dead.
Joe's essentially dead to me.
Oona and I broke up.
-You broke…
-You don't actually wanna be my sister.
It was fun for you in theory.
but now that it's real. you don't.
You're freaking out.
Okay. None of that is true.
Just feels like my dad
is more your dad now than mine.
So I'm sorry that I'm not having
a perfect reaction to that.
This is your home. Ramona.
You love it here.
What if I just love it
because I don't know anything else?
This is the best place in the world.
You always say that.
You've seen everything. Annie.
And Gordon. he was.
like. traumatized by his daughter dying.
and then…
he was stuck here.
Like. he couldn't leave.
and he instilled all these morals
and values into me.
and I don't know
if they were important to me. though.
Like. actually. at my core.
I don't know if I believe in them.
And. like. selling this place would just…
It would… It would change my life.
Yeah. Yeah.
I totally understand that.
Um.
I'm sorry.
I ju… I. um…
I don't know that it's worth the money
to sell your home
-because there's so many options. Ramona.
-You've had everything!
You've had everything!
I see the face creams. man.
You've never had to worry about a thing.
It's not bad for me to want
this bigger life for myself.
That's not bad at all.
But a bigger life
can be a lot harder. actually.
[Ramona] So can a small one!
If you're thinking about New York.
I don't know
how much you're gonna like it. Ramona.
It's not an easy place to live.
even for me.
It's why I might want to stay here.
This was Mom's place. and she wanted--
[scoffs] Mom's dead. Mom's dead.
We can't ask her what she wanted.
I don't know. You don't know.
Annie. she grew up here.
and then she left.
[Annie] And then she came back.
You know what? I'm… Let's. um…
Why don't we take a night and sleep on it?
-No. No. I'm sorry. No.
-And just…
My mind's not gonna be changed
in the morning.
Ramona. you can't make
a decision this big in one day.
Just take… Just take a second.
[Ramona] Because all that matters
is what you want.
You don't want me to sell. but you sure
as shit don't want me in New York.
You fucking promised.
Okay.
Okay?
I did promise.
I did promise. I said
I'd do whatever you want. so I will.
Okay.
-Thank you.
-Mmm-hmm.
["Rain" playing]
Ramona?
[Ramona] Yeah?
Are… Are you sleeping in there?
[Ramona] Yeah.
[Ramona] You don't remember anything?
[sighing]
[Annie] I mean. like. one thing.
but it's like…
I don't really know if it's. like.
an actual memory
or just. like. a picture
or a story someone told me.
so it's probably not real.
We're laying in bed.
and she's scratching my back.
like. scratchies. you know?
And I can feel her breathing.
and it's like…
Like. I just felt very warm and. like.
so safe and held.
There you go.
[chattering indistinctly]
[laughing softly]
Thank you.
Mom?
It's okay.
…down lazy river.
That'll be good.
And then we can go…
Yeah!
-[speaking indistinctly]
-[both laugh]
Hi.
Honey. come here. Come on.
[Goldie laughing faintly]
I'm so sorry.
[sniffing]
It's okay.
-[Annie] Ramona?
-Hmm?
I can't do it. I'm sorry.
Can't do what?
[Annie] Can we just wait a year?
Please? I feel like
I'm just getting to know Mom.
And I didn't realize how badly
I needed this place. But I really do.
I can't believe this.
I'm only asking you for a year.
I feel like I'm gonna die
if I spend another year here.
I know that you're really hurt right now.
and I'm so sorry about that.
But you're 16. Ramona.
and if you sell this place.
you'll be making
the biggest mistake of your life.
I swear to God. Please. I want you
to think clearly about this.
I'm thinking clearly. Very clearly.
So am I.
I really. really feel that Mom would
want us both to be here together.
Really? Do you? You really think that?
Or do you maybe think
the way that I think?
Which is. I'm kind of discovering
that my life is fucking. like.
bullshit. and I wanna see something new.
But now I'm stuck here
because you don't want to sell?
I can't. I can't. I'm sorry.
Right. Right. Right.
Ramona. I'm leaving today…
[door slams]
[cell phone ringing]
Hello?
[female voice]
Hi. Is this Connor Jacobson?
Yeah.
Hi. Connor. This is Dawn Fisher
from Open Hearts Adoption Agency.
We got a response from
your biological mother about your request.
And she would love
to get in touch with you.
Hey. Maple.
[Maple] Hi.
Is she here? I wanna talk to her.
Um.
no.
Know when she'll be back?
Okay. Well. um…
if you see her. let her know
I'm stuck here forever.
if she ever wants to talk.
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Sorry.
Yeah.
Yeah. me too.
[Maple] You know how messed up
it is to ask a child to lie?
Yeah. I know.
I'm sorry. And thank you.
Why didn't you want to talk to her?
If she knew that I was here.
she wouldn't do what she needs to do.
Well. what does she need to do?
She needs to do what's best for her.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah. I'm good.
Hi.
Hey.
I think Ellis is out there
getting the plane ready for you.
-Okay. Thank you. Cool.
-He should be back soon.
Cool.
I had a dream about my mom last night.
Yeah?
You think she regretted
blowing up her life?
No. I think maybe she would've done things
a little bit differently. but no.
She was…
She was finally happy.
In fact. she told me
that she wished she had done it sooner.
So what happened between
when my dad took us and when my mom died?
-Was she gonna come back ever?
-Of course she was comin' back.
She had a ticket to New York
two days after you left.
Soonest one she could get.
-Really?
-Yeah.
So then was it the stress
of my dad taking us
that caused her to go
into an early labor or--
No.
-Well. how could it not have been?
-No. no. no. [sighs]
The doctor said no.
Okay?
She had a heart condition.
I mean. nobody knew.
So. like…
what exactly happened that night?
[sighing] Annie. uh…
I'm sorry. I…
Okay.
She was…
She was in pain.
And she didn't know if it was contractions
or not. you know. so…
I rushed her to the hospital.
I remember thinking that…
There was no way this boat
could move slower. you know.
but we were flying across the lake.
I kept pushing it.
I actually bent the throttle.
And we got there.
And I just remember
all these doctors and nurses.
It was packed.
And I kept getting pushed out.
And so I was standing in the doorway.
and I heard this crash.
I remember I looked down the hall.
and this doctor.
he was older than everyone else.
came flyin' around the corner.
and he ran into this medical cart.
and shit went flyin' everywhere.
And he sprinted
right past me into the room.
and I remember that
that is when it dawned on me
that this was bad. you know?
And they. uh. took her into surgery.
Surgery? What s… What sur…
I didn't know she had surgery.
She had an emergency C-section.
I didn't know she had a C-section.
[sighs]
Was she… Was she scared?
You know. your mom.
she was the bravest. most fearless person
I had ever known.
And when they were taking her
out of the room. we made eye contact.
and I remember she smiled at me.
you know. like she was gonna reassure me.
[chuckles sadly]
And then what happened?
Well. then I never saw her again.
She didn't come out of surgery.
So she never got to meet Ramona?
Or hold her? Anything like that?
No.
["Don't Think Twice.
It's Alright" playing]
Hi.
I'm so glad you're here. I was…
You know. I was hoping
I could… see you before I left.
-Um…
-Yeah.
I don't know where your head is or if…
there's a world where maybe…
you and I could spend some time together.
'Cause I really wanna…
[sentimental music playing]
Ramona?
You've been girl
with dead mom your whole life.
Okay.
And you've always had this place and her…
all of her memories
and Gordon and… I mean…
You slept in her bed every summer.
Like. that's…
That's so incredible.
I want that.
I need to be girl with dead mom too.
And you've never gotten
to be girl with an alive dad.
And I have had that.
For 18 years. I've had that.
Ho…
And honestly. he's a really good dad.
And I want you to have that.
And I really do want you to have that.
["Fleeting" playing]
You deserve to be taken care of.
Yeah. No. I know I deserve that.
I just… I don't know if I want it.
Well. I think…
I think you need it.
How do you know what I need?
Because I'm your sister.
[Ramona] So what should we do?
[slow instrumental music playing]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org